# Manisha Korala

 ♀ Islamabad, Pakistan ■ tanwani.manisha@gmail.com □ +92-335-0515093 Im https://www.linkedin.com/in/manisha-korala/

#### SUMMARY

Software Engineer with 3+ years of experience in designing, building, and testing application systems. Seeking a competitive role in software development through working among a productive and creative team to utilize and polish my technical skills with an opportunity to build production-ready systems.

### **EXPERIENCE**

#### Stack Developer

#### Automotive Artificial Intelligence, Islamabad

April 2018 - Present

- Developed and released the web application for the company's core product for testing 100% Autonomous Driving Systems.
- · Gathered client requirements and handle CR's (change requests) to improve the user's experience for customers.
- · Communicated with a cross country team to ensure timely deliveries with the primary focus on application design and delivery.
- · Acted as the Scrum Master and led daily standup in an agile environment to manage a team of 3 developers.

#### Software Engineer

Arkhitech, Islamabad

July 2017 - March 2018

- Collaborated with a cross-functional team of 5 to implement end-to-end applications for 2 different client projects.
- Engaged with clients to collect requirements, developed the project scope, and created concepts.
- Co-ordinated in a team to revamp the company's management system for handling activities of 50+ employees reducing manual efforts by 90%.

### Java Developer Intern

#### QUEST LAB, FAST-NUCES, Islamabad

June 2016 - August 2016

- · Applied ETL (extract, transform, load) operations on 3+ sources of data to extract meaningful information.
- Wrote 200+ automated test cases for large scale underdeveloped applications in selenium.

### **PROJECTS**

### AAI Replica [Python Flask, Vue.js, Node.js, SQLAlchemy]

A simulation platform to support safer and faster development of highly automated driving and allows to test the boundaries of autonomous driving software in highly customizable test configurations.

### 8020 Connect [Ruby on Rails, RSpec]

8020 Connect is an investment industry's social media platform for the interactive sharing of knowledge and ideas between industry professionals, public companies, and individual investors.

### MonitorCop [Android, Firebase]

An android based parental control mobile application to allow parents to monitor and restrict the activities on a child's smartphone to give a safer technology experience.

## **EDUCATION**

# **Bachelor of Science (Computer Science)**

2013 - 2017

National University of Computer and Emerging Sciences • Islamabad, Pakistan.

### **SKILLS**

Language: Python, JavaScript (ES9), HTML5/CSS3

Technologies: Flask, Vue.js, Node.js, Express, Bootstrap, MVC Framework

Database: SQLAlchemy, MySQL, Express

Others: Git, GitFlow, Rest API, JIRA, PyCharm, Visual Studio

### **HONORS & AWARDS**

- · Honorable mention in Dean's List
- Scholarship for TUM's training as a Software Engineer
- Traveled internationally on an official business trip
- Microsoft Student Partner Microsoft (Fast NUCES, Islamabad)